On Sunday April 16, 2017, during the Live
Service at The SCOAN, Prophet T.B. Joshua
showed appreciation for the prayers of people
around the world following his prophecy the
previous week.
He also gave further insight into world affairs.
This is what he said.
"I want to thank you for your prayers.
Viewers all over the world, thank you for
your prayers; I need to thank you.
I want to thank you, in a very big way.
On Thursday, I was in the (prayer) mountain but I could see the atmosphere all over - prayer and fasting!
I thank you for honouring the voice of a Prophet.
Many people went for two days fasting and
they came back on Friday night.
I was very happy.
When I saw these people, I said, "No, the
record will be changed".
What I was seeing that Thursday and I said,
'Please, fast and pray on Thursday and Friday'
That particular Thursday, if not for your
prayers, I don't know what would have happened.
But you have seen the sign.
North Korea will still test it.
The one they tested; the will still test another
one.
They are not going to give up - but God is
in control.
What I saw on Thursday when I asked you to
fast: I said, "I am seeing a big temptation
that will cause arguments in the superpower
community'.
Before the thing was thrown, I had seen it
already.
What is this, the biggest bomb?
I saw it before I said it.
Two weeks before that time, I saw the biggest
bomb.
That was why on Sunday, I cried out and said, 'Please, what I'm seeing on Thursday, Friday - fast!'
I saw the biggest bomb and another superpower
was saying they have the biggest!
The sign, which you have seen - when the bomb
called the 'Mother Of All Bombs' was thrown,
the Russians said they have the 'Father Of
All Bombs'.
Is that not trouble?
I said, 'What I'm seeing -
it will provoke'.
I continued saying this since 2016.
Once again, I want to thank you for that Thursday.
I said you should fast and pray on Friday.
I was very specific because I saw it.
If you saw what happened in the Spirit, you
would know that God loves you.
Viewers all over the world, thank you."